[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although discovered in the United States, Plutos name came from Europe - it was suggested by Falconer Maden, a former librarian at the Oxford University Bodleian Library.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Aztecs are known for wearing hummingbird talismans which symbolize which of the following?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Skill at arms", "Energy", "Sexual potency"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This film is about the 5 Lisbon sisters who lived in Grosse Pointe, Michigan in the 1970s.", "correct_answer": "The Virgin Suicides", "incorrect_answers": ["A Map of the World", "Beautiful People", "The Loss of Sexual Innocence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the movie Benny and Joon come out?", "correct_answer": "1993", "incorrect_answers": ["1990", "1996", "1987"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these quotes is from the 1995 movie Apollo 13?", "correct_answer": "Houston, we have a problem.", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Damn, do you copy me at all?", "I have a bad feeling about all this."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The pregnancy of this animal lasts from 2 to 3 years depending on the altitude it inhabits.", "correct_answer": "Alpine Salamander", "incorrect_answers": ["Spanish Imperial Eagle", "Asian Elephant", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Because of its unique properties in interacting with other substances, water is often referred to as the universal what?", "correct_answer": "Solvent", "incorrect_answers": ["Stabilizer", "Neutralizer", "Oxidant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word for tomato in Spanish is _________ .", "correct_answer": "el tomate", "incorrect_answers": ["el labio", "la manzana", "el escritorio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the character played by Stacy Keach in Cheech and Chongs movies Up In Smoke and Nice Dreams?", "correct_answer": "Sgt. Stedenko", "incorrect_answers": ["Det. Stedenko", "Sgt. Bilko", "Capt. Tedesco"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is referred to by the term fourth world (in contrast to the better-known terms first world, second world and third world?", "correct_answer": "disenfranchised societies", "incorrect_answers": ["interplanetary societies", "undiscovered societies", "global societies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Razor box trap in Saw II was meant for Gus.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the original title considered by director Stanley Kubrick for his 1968 movie 2001: A Space Odyssey, the greatest science fiction movie according to the American Film Institute?", "correct_answer": "Journey Beyond the Stars", "incorrect_answers": ["Space Mission", "A Man and His Galaxy", "Deep Space"]}]